var questions = [{
  "question": "What movie has one the most Golden Globe Awards with seven?",
  "option1": "La La Land",
  "option2": "A Star is Born",
  "option3": "The Godfather",
  "option4": "Doctor Zhivago",
  "answer": "1"
}, {
  "question": "Which celebrity was not born in the U.S?",
  "option1": "Arnold Schwarzenegger",
  "option2": "Chris Pratt",
  "option3": "Micheal Jordan",
  "option4": "Kanye West",
  "answer": "1"
}, {
  "question": "Which of these shows has been hosted by Jimmy Fallon since 2014?",
  "option1": "The Late Show",
  "option2": "Late Night",
  "option3": "The Daily Show",
  "option4": "The Tonight Show",
  "answer": "4"
}, {
  "question": "Which of these musicals was not composed by Andrew Lloyd Webber?",
  "option1": "Jesus Christ Supertar",
  "option2": "Chicago",
  "option3": "Cats",
  "option4": "The Phantom of the Opera",
  "answer": "2"
}, {
  "question": "What Broadway show includes characters such as Riff, Tony, and Maria?",
  "option1": "Rent",
  "option2": "West Side Story",
  "option3": "Hairspray",
  "option4": "Grease",
  "answer": "2"
}, {
  "question": "Which of these entertainment mediums is a TV show?",
  "option1": "30 Rock",
  "option2": "Evita",
  "option3": "Office Space",
  "option4": "A Day in the Life",
  "answer": "1"
}, {
  "question": "Which of these quotes is not from a Star Wars movie?",
  "option1": "No, I am your father.",
  "option2": "May the force be with you.",
  "option3": "That's no moon.",
  "option4": "Here's Johnny!",
  "answer": "4"
}, {
  "question": "Which of these comic book superheroes does not belong to Marvel?",
  "option1": "Wonder Woman",
  "option2": "The Hulk",
  "option3": "Deadpool",
  "option4": "Ant-Man",
  "answer": "1"
}, {
  "question": "What anime features characters that can become 'Super Saiyan'?",
  "option1": "Naruto",
  "option2": "Dragon Ball Z",
  "option3": "One Piece",
  "option4": "One Punch Man",
  "answer": "2"
}, {
  "question": "Which of these superhero ensembles belongs to DC Comics?",
  "option1": "The Avengers",
  "option2": "The Justice League",
  "option3": "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",
  "option4": "X-Men",
  "answer": "2"

}

];